https://www.dollhousedreams.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Privacy Policy
Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys respects your privacy. Consistent with our commitment to providing you with a satisfying shopping experience, we have found that collecting Personal Information (defined below) through DollhouseDreams.com and providing you with the opportunity to provide us with information as a result of your purchase from Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys (referred to in this Privacy Policy as the "Store"), helps us better understand the products and services most helpful to you. Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we gather and how we use this information. Please read this information carefully.
By accessing DollhouseDreams.com and providing us with your information you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. Accordingly, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the bottom of this page) and review any changes since the last version. If at any time you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site and refrain from purchasing from us.
Data collected from our store is the property of the store. If you have questions about a store’s privacy policies, please contact the store directly.
Use of Information Collected by Us
We may collect two types of information about users: "Personal Information" (such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, mobile phone number, credit card number and the items you purchase) and "Aggregate Information" (such as information about how many users log on to our Site on a daily basis.
We use customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, promotions and contests. We may also use this information to present offers to you, to help us target specific products and services to you, and to help us develop and improve our Site and tailor our Site to your interests.
Personal Information Collected Online and Via Mobile by DollhouseDreams.com
Personal Information is collected online and via mobile by us when users voluntarily register with DollhouseDreams.com or via our mobile site and applications to purchase items, receive electronic newsletters, SMS, MMS and text messages, use community and communication services, answer surveys and enter contests and other promotional opportunities provided by DollhouseDreams.com, when users make a purchase, and when users utilize the "Email to a Friend" or SMS, MMS or Text features. We also maintain a record of your product interests and purchases online and via mobile. We may receive personal usage and demographic information from third parties we work with. When you make an online purchase we collect information about you. We use this information to market our products and services to you, by adding you to our email, SMS, MMS and Text promotions and campaigns.
Aggregate Information Collected Online by DollhouseDreams.com Online and Via Our Mobile Site
Aggregate Information is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about you, such as age, gender, types of products purchased, frequency of visits, Site pages you access most frequently or search terms you enter. Aggregate Information is used in a collective manner, and no single person can be identified by that compiled information. For example, the number of people who shopped at DollhouseDreams.com and via our mobile site during a specific time period is Aggregate Information that does not personally identify a specific user. Both DollhouseDreams.com and our mobile site collect Aggregate Information.
Order-related and Promotional email, SMS, TEXT and MMS Messages
If You opt-in, You agree that Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys, DollhouseDreams.com and our mobile site is authorized to transmit email, SMS, MMS and Text Messages to you for the purpose of informing you about your particular transaction. In addition, DollhouseDreams.com may offer electronic newsletters and promotional emails, SMS, MMS and TEXT Messages to those who have agreed to receive emails and these other types of messages during registration or directly from our email and/or mobile sign-up form. Unsubscribe and opt down instructions are included in each promotional email and mobile message.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
We do not share, sell or trade with third parties your Personal Information gathered online or via mobile, such as email addresses or mobile phone numbers, Personal Information collected as part of an online survey or other specific details about you, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy. We do not contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to such Personal Information.
The Personal Information and Aggregate Information we collect may be shared with reputable third-party organizations to contact consumers for marketing and promotional purposes. Third party contacts to our customers may be initiated only by postal mail. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your telephone number(s) or e-mail address.
We may divulge Personal Information if such action is required for Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys to comply with any valid legal process, such as a subpoena, search warrant, statute or court order, or any valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency. In addition, we may divulge Personal Information if we or any of our service providers or consultants believes that such disclosure is necessary to address any unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of another customer or of the general public.
Service Providers
We may share Personal Information and Aggregate Information with our service providers, consultants and affiliates for our internal business purposes. For example, we use the services of Google, Inc (www.google.com) to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Site. The type of information we collect includes products viewed and/or purchased, your location (state/zip code if you placed an order) and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. The computers, which deliver the Web pages to you, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from our Site, our servers log your IP address. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that Web sites, when you visit them, often store on your hard drive. A cookie may contain information (such as unique user ID), which is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited.
DollhouseDreams.com and our mobile site use cookies to preserve the contents of your shopping cart between your visits. DollhouseDreams.com and our mobile site also use cookies to measure activity on our Site, which allows us to determine which areas and features of our Site is the most popular. This information allows us to make improvements and updates to enhance your DollhouseDreams.com and mobile experiences. Parts of the Sites, such as the members-only areas (for example, shopping) will not function if you do not have cookies enabled. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you turn off cookies or refuse them, though, you will not be able to make a purchase from the Site, nor will we be able to recognize you as a registered user to allow you access to your account information.
To enable or disable cookies on your browser, please consult your browser documentation or contact your software provider.
Security and SSL
Protecting your order information is a priority for us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower right-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active and the server is secure. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the Site address will change from "http" to "https." Some versions of browsers and some firewalls don't permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you won't be able to connect to the server and therefore won't be able to place an order through a secure connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please print our shopping page and place your order by phone at (877) 875-6500.
Information Removal/Opt-Out
If you prefer not to receive marketing emails, SMS, MMS or Text Messages from DollhouseDreams.com, please let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any marketing email, SMS, MMS or Text Message you receive from us.
Children and Privacy
We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet, and understand that children may not understand all the provisions of our Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit.
We will never request personally identifiable information from anyone whom we know to be under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a customer is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files.
Links to Other Sites
DollhouseDreams.com, may contain links to sites other than our own. Those sites may have their own privacy policy or no privacy policy at all. We do not have any responsibility for those sites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience of our visitors. Such links may be to advertisers, content providers or other companies as a result of an agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you and may collect information and use it in a way inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third-party sites or services before providing any of them with any of your Personal Information. Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys does not control the content that appears on these sites or take any responsibility for their content, nor should it be implied that Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys, DollhouseDreams.com or our mobile site endorse or otherwise recommend such sites or their products or services offered.
Additional Information
No transmission of data over the Internet or via Mobile is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys, DollhouseDreams.com and our mobile site to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect Your Personal Information, neither Dollhouse Dreams/Miniatures & Toys, DollhouseDreams.com and our mobile site can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the Internet. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.
Limitation on Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL DOLLHOUE DREAMS/MINIATURES & TOYS, DOLLHOUSEDREAMS.COM BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, EVEN IF THESE ENTITIES HAVE BEEN PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION, UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR ANY OTHER THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, INABILITY TO USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS AND MATERIALS AVAILABLE FROM THE SITE. These limitations shall apply notwithstanding any failure of essential purpose or the existence of any limited remedy. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on how long an implied warranty lasts, or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, the above limitations may not apply to you.
Applicable Law
The laws of the State of Iowa will govern these disclaimers, terms and conditions without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.
Last modified: Jan 8, 2015
Sign up for our Newsletter:
Your Name:
Melissa & Doug The Bear Factory Learning Resources Animaland Pawsenclaws & CO Usborne Books
View all brands
Recent Updates
Kids test toys at Dollhouse Dreams
Who better to test toys than the ones who will be using them? And with this in …
Dollhouse Dreams up and running after storm damage
FORT MADISON, Ia. (WGEM) -
A Fort Madison business is back home …
A Trip to Dollhouse Dreams
10 year old April Norton recently visited Dollhouse Dreams.  "Dollhouse …
Facebook
All prices are in USD
Copyright 2020 Dollhouse Dreams Miniatures & Toys.
Sitemap |
